const questions = [
    { question: "What is a professional traffic permit?",
    answer: "Traffic permits are a requirement for conducting professional traffic."
    },
    { question: "How to check the traffic condition?",
    answer: "Answer2"
    },
    { question: "What are the requirements for a professional traffic permit?",
    answer: "Answer3"
    },
    { question: "Are there professional traffic permit training courses at a distance?",
    answer: "Answer4"
    },
    { question: "When is a professional traffic permit needed?",
    answer: "Answer5"
    },
    { question: "Where to look for a traffic permit?",
    answer: "Answer6"
    },
    { question: "Are there differences between a traffic permit and a professional traffic permit?",
    answer: "Answer7"
    },
    { question: "How much does a commercial traffic permit cost for goods?",
    answer: "Answer8"
    },
    { question: "How to plug in for the traffic permit test?",
    answer: "Answer9"
    },
    { question: "How is the sample for a professional traffic permit booked?",
    answer: "Answer10"
    }
]